dealerease.net 2006-06-19

# Privacy Policy

At Dealerease® we take your privacy very seriously. The following contains information on how we collect, gather, and identify information while on Dealerease.net This information may be updated as we change or develop our site.

Personally Identifiable Information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, phone number, email or postal address. In many cases we need this information to provide the service that you have requested.

The amount of Personally Identifiable Information that you choose to disclose to Dealerease® is completely up to you. The only way we know something about you personally is if you provide it to us in conjunction with one of our services.

**What information do we collect and how do we use it?**

Dealerease® collects information on our users in several ways: by your voluntary submissions and through cookies. You can decline this exchange of information on any site on the Internet - not just ours - at any time. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the services dependent upon the collection of this information.

The information Dealerease® collects is used in a variety of ways: for internal review; to improve the content of the site, thus making your user experience more valuable; to notify you about updates to the service; and to let you know about products and services that you may be interested in.

******What does Dealerease® do with the information it gathers/tracks?**

The information is used by Dealerease® to contact Dealers for its own marketing endeavors. As a valued consumer, we offer you the opportunity to "opt out", or request not to accept these marketing opportunities. If at any time you change your mind and do not want Dealerease® to share your email address or would simply like to be removed from the list, please let us know by emailing us at: [remove@Dealerease.net](mailto:remove@dealerease.net)

******Cookies**

Dealerease® may automatically collect non-personally identifiable information and data through the use of "Cookies or Session ID's" Cookies are small text files a Web site uses to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to the site and facilitate the use of the site. "Cookies" also allow a site to track usage behavior and compile site usage information that will allow for the improvement of content and target advertising.

Some sites in the Dealerease® System use Overture and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web sites. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (i.e. not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Dealerease® is committed to the safety of children. Children under 18 may not participate in or use Dealerease® in any way shape or form on unless given parental consent.

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of the information described in this Privacy Policy by Dealerease®. Your continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of our privacy policy.
